myoggy.com 2011-11-09

# MyOggy.Com Submit Create Share and Post your business, articles, website, blogs.

| 

**MyOggy.Com Privacy Policy**

Guardian Angel Enterprises LLC (from hereon ‘we’ ‘our’ or ‘us’) operates MyOggy.com, and also has the DBA MyOggy.com and MyOggy. This Privacy Policy describes MyOggy’s use and sharing of personally identifiable information (“PII”-- your full name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, or credit card number) that Members (any and all users who register an account with MyOggy.Com) voluntarily provide to MyOggy when they register (also known PII). The term user refers to a visitor to the website, or a Member. This Privacy Policy applies to all services, applications, features, content offered by MyOggy.com at the MyOggy.Com website.   MyOggy.Com is hosted in the United States.

MyOggy.com is for a  general audience site and does not knowingly or intentionally collect PII from children under 14 years of age.

We may modify this privacy policy, our services, features, applications, or practices as deemed necessary or as desired.   Any changes or modifications are effective upon posting by us on the MyOggy.com website.  Continued use of the site by any visitor or member constitutes your agreement and acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy.  It is your responsibility to review the Privacy Policy to ensure you are updated on any changes.

PII collected at the MyOggy.com website is collected because it is voluntarily submitted to us for you to register as a member of MyOggy.com.  Additionally, MyOggy.com may also collect personal information from people, members, or visitors that may choose to voluntarily participate in any of MyOggy.com’s promotions, surveys, contests, polls, or other activities or features which may request personal information, because you want to be provided with products, services, information, updates, or in connection with content, feedback submitted to MyOggy.com for review and/ or response.  Additionally MyOggy.com collects other information such as and including IP address, and aggregate user data which is used to track usage, to manage and improve services, and/ or for security purposes.  Other personal information collected and submitted voluntarily to MyOggy.com includes information within their personal MyOggy webspace and profiles which can include but is not limited to birthdate, interests, activities, hobbies, likes, dislikes, gender, lifestyles, photographs, videos, employments, schools, educations, personal statements, beliefs, affiliated groups, companies or businesses (Personal Profile Information).  

MyOggy.com members have control to change their PII or Personal Profile Information at will, and can further control privacy settings which control how other users, members, and visitors to MyOggy.com will be able to search for them, view their information, and/ or communicate with them.  Profile changes can be made under “Profile”, and “Edit Profile Information” or “Change Profile Photo”.  Members can change their privacy settings by going to the “settings” tab and clicking on “Privacy Options”.  MyOggy.com may use cookies or information provided to customize online advertisements you encounter while on MyOggy.com, better aligning them to your interests, hobbies, or favorite activities, etc.

Cookies. Cookies are small bits of information that MyOggy.com places on your computer. MyOggy.com uses cookies to identify your Internet browser, store Users’ preferences, and determine whether you have installed the enabling software needed to access certain material, applications, features, or services on the MyOggy.com website. Data in cookies may be read to authenticate user sessions or provide or improve services.

Third party advertisements displayed on MyOggy.com website may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies, advertisers, and/ or third parties.  These cookies are known as third-party cookies.  MyOggy.com has no control over third party cookies and users, members, or visitors should check the individual privacy policies of the advertisers or internet advertising company to determine if and how it may use cookies.   MyOggy.com may further use tags or scripts which are for purposes of tracking and reporting the number of page views, types and/ or origin of page views, for any or each page.  This information is used to manage and improve services, for advertising, to determine trends, to improve or modify services.  Your computer can be programmed to give warning of cookies or to block all or third party cookies.  Blocking all cookies may prevent you from accessing features, applications, or services provided by MyOggy.com

Members provide their email address when signing up for MyOggy.com services and use.  Administrators will use this email address to contact members about their account, about it's services, added features, new contests, or for any reason related to MyOggy.com.  Additionally MyOggy.com will send automated email notifications when certain actions are made to and from members and friends on MyOggy.com.  Members have control in which activity notifications they wish to receive or not receive, in the "settings" section when logged into their account.

MyOggy.com will not share your PII with third parties except for where it is described within this privacy policy, unless you have given us permission to do so.

MyOggy.com is linked to other websites operated by other companies, and we are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any other websites or services from third parties or internet advertising companies.  Once you leave the MyOggy.com website via a link such as a widget or advertisement, you should check on applicable privacy practices for any third party website to determine whether it’s present or acceptable.  Some widgets, services, features or games may be offered from third parties and you must check with those third parties to determine their privacy policies and practices, as MyOggy.com has no control over the privacy practices of any other company or third party.

One of the features that MyOggy.com offers is a search tool, which allows people, visitors, or members to search for people they know using search fields correlating to certain profile fields such as first and last name, former name, city and state, etc.  You have control over choosing to not allow your profile information be returned in search results, through the privacy options under the “settings” tab.  Choosing to not allow your profile information to be returned in searches, means that other people will not be able to find you in MyOggy.com through the search tool. Further MyOggy.com has a feature which may suggest common friends links with other friends, suggesting “you may know this person”, which is designed to help members find people or friends they might know but otherwise may not have found or connected with.  MyOggy.com also has a feature which sends automatic email notifications when certain actions have taken place in your network, and you have control of which emails you receive in your “settings” area, where you can choose to turn on or off any or all email notifications.  MyOggy.com may contact you relating to your membership, your account, our services, features, applications, or operations.

MyOggy.com members and business administrators, or affiliated companies must have a business reason to have access to members’ PII.  We may share your personal information or PII with other businesses, contractors, agents, sponsors, advertisers or companies in order to help us modify or improve our services, features, applications, or to analyze data, trends, or to help us with administration of any features or services, or to determine and analyze for purposes of judgements, awarding prizes, in contests and surveys.  These companies or third party contractors may temporarily store some information but only to provide MyOggy.com with it’s intended services and not for any other reason.  These outside contractors, agents or sponsors may temporarily store some information on their servers, but they may only use your PII to provide MyOggy.com with a specific service and not for any other purpose. MyOggy.com may also provide your PII to a third party in those instances where you have chosen to receive certain information and have been notified that the fulfillment of such a request requires the sharing of your PII. MyOggy.com also may share your PII with Affiliated Companies if it has a business reason to do so.

MyOggy.com may share or disclose PII, information or profile information to protect or defend legal rights, safety and security of the website and users and members, in risk management, or to comply with the law or court order.

Additionally if MyOggy.com is involved in a sale, or transaction, or merger which involves another party taking control of all or any part of MyOggy.com, then we may transfer PII, profile information, and database to the party or parties involved in the transaction.

MyOggy.com will only use the PII you provide under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

Members, Users, or visitors that choose to post information publicly, submit information, or use MyOggy.com in any way, are responsible for checking into governing laws within the country they reside, and are responsible for ensuring that such information conforms to local data protection laws.

MyOggy.com uses reasonable administrative, and technical measures to protect and safeguard PII in it’s possession against fraud, theft, loss, or unauthorized use.

Members have access to the personal information, PII, and profile information and privacy settings that are associated with their account and may update their accounts as deemed necessary.  If you choose to close your account, MyOggy.com will honor your request while still maintaining information necessary to comply with state, federal or applicable laws.

Guardian Angel Enterprises LLC

20805 State Route 410E #454

Bonney Lake, WA  98391

|
